https://www.brandchannel.com/privacy-and-terms-of-service

Skip to content
1) PRIVACY POLICY:
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for brandchannel and applies to the information collected on our website at https://www.brandchannel.com.
brandchannel respects your right to privacy in the personal information you provide us on our website. To that end, unless you designate otherwise or we state otherwise in this policy or at the time information is collected, any personal information you provide in registering for our site and/or newsletter will be known only to two parties: you and brandchannel. The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our site and our newsletter.
Personal information includes your name, e-mail address, click-through activity, and any other personal information you may provide here. This policy may be updated to reflect new products and service offerings, so please check back periodically.
brandchannel and its parent company, Interbrand, are the sole owner of the information collected on this website and our email newsletter. We only have access to/collect information you voluntarily give us through signing up for our newsletter or direct contact. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you in the future, via email, to inform you about new articles, features, or other items of interest to the brandchannel community—or to tell you about updates to our privacy policy.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, please contact us immediately at 212-798-7802 or via an email us at editor@brandchannel.com.
Traffic data
Each time a visitor comes to brandchannel.com, our server—like most websites—collects basic technical information, including, for example, your domain name (e.g., whether the user has logged on from yahoo.com or whitehouse.gov), referral data (e.g., we record the address of the last URL a user visited prior to clicking through to brandchannel.com) and browser and platform type (e.g., a Chrome browser on an Android platform).
We also count, track and aggregate visitors activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our site (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the site, etc.). To these ends, we may merge information about visitors and visits into group data, but we will not disclose your individual identity or personally identifiable data without your permission.
In the event that we may present aggregated information to third parties, we do so only in the format of anonymous statistics, meaning that no one will ever be able to identify you or contact you.
Email subscriptions
If you would like to unsubscribe from the brandchannel email list, please follow the instructions at the footer of each email newsletter. Any queries may be addressed to editor@brandchannel.com.
Comments
We welcome the views and opinions of our readers and encourage a respectful, lively dialogue on our site. If you choose to comment on brandchannel.com, we do not sell or redistribute your personal information and will not contact a provided email address, except in rare cases to reply to or clarify your comment. Name and affiliation (but not email address) will be posted along with the comment, unless otherwise requested (in which case the comment will appear from anonymous). Participants are expected to comply with the rules governing the comment sections. We cannot, however, control how third parties use information that commenters choose to provide in our public forum. We have the absolute right to remove any comments we deem to be offensive, spam or otherwise inappropriate.
White papers
The views and opinions in white papers are not necessarily those of brandchannel or its staff. brandchannel is not responsible for editing or proofing any white papers posted on our site. Any inaccuracies or mistakes are those of the author(s) alone. Materials submitted with excessive grammatical or spelling errors will not be considered for posting.
Surveys
We may from time to time conduct voluntary surveys of visitors to the site to obtain readers’ opinions. Such information may be compiled and shared in the aggregate with third parties, but no personal details will be traceable or associated with specific individuals.
Other disclosure of personal information
We will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except (i) as described in this privacy policy, or (ii) as required by law, court order or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority (i.e., Against our will).
Links and other sites
We link to other sites and content on the web, and cannot control (nor are we responsible for) their privacy practices or content. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of those sites.
Security
brandchannel takes precautions to protect your information (both online and offline) as a reader, contributor or participant on our site.
2) TERMS OF SERVICE
This website is copyrighted by Interbrand on behalf of brandchannel, all rights reserved.
The views and opinions expressed on brandchannel are not necessarily those of its parent company, Interbrand, or Omnicom or any of its member companies.
Certain material contained on this website may be licensed from third parties, and any copyrights, trademarks or service marks in such content belong to the respective third parties.
This website and its content, whether statement, expression of opinion or any other matter herein, are not an offer to sell or a solicitation of an offer to buy any security, nor shall any such security be offered or sold to any person, in any jurisdiction in which such offer, solicitation, purchase, or sale may not lawfully be made.
Please note that brandchannel does not sign non-disclosure agreements and that business information shared in any form with the firm, its employees, and affiliates cannot be considered confidential.
The information contained in this site is taken from sources believed to be reliable, but its accuracy cannot be guaranteed.
brandchannel, its principals, employees, contributors and partners may at any time hold positions and options in companies discussed herein, and may provide consulting and other services to those companies.
brandchannel and Interbrand reserve the right to change this Terms of Service and Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice.
Additional questions:
If you have any further questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy and use of personal information or our Terms of Service, please email inquiries@interbrand.com.
If you have additional questions about brandchannel, please visit the About Us section of this website.
If you have any questions about brandchannel parent Interbrand, please visit Interbrand.com.
Updated 3/15/15
The latest news.The expert analysis.Delivered directly to you.
most popular:
5 Questions with Diego Zaccaria, Creative Director of the Centre du Graphisme
BGB
term of the day:
brand strength
An integral part of Interbrand’s brand valuation methodology, brand strength is a detailed assessment designed to decide if the brand’s forecast earnings will be read more:
5 questions
news
features
glossary
brandspeak
subscribe
search
